<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>medicine on Halal Food Guide from Authentic Scholars</title>
    <link>https://askhalal.ca/tags/medicine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in medicine on Halal Food Guide from Authentic Scholars</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://askhalal.ca/tags/medicine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nasal Spray</title>
      <link>https://askhalal.ca/products/nasalspray/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askhalal.ca/products/nasalspray/</guid>
      <description>These Nasal Sprays are reviewed by the IlmHub Team Drixoral (Oxymetazoline HCl 0.5%) Each spray or pump bottle contains: oxymetazoline HCl 0.05% in aqueous solution. Nonmedicinal ingredients: benzalkonium chloride, edetate disodium, propylene glycol, water and pH adjusted with hydrochloric acid or sodium hydroxide. Conventional spray bottles of 20 mL and metered pump sprays of 25 mL.
Dristan Nasal Mist (Oxymetazoline HCL .05%) Dristan Long Lasting Nasal Mist: Each bottle contains: oxymetazoline HCl 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pain Killers</title>
      <link>https://askhalal.ca/products/painkillers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askhalal.ca/products/painkillers/</guid>
      <description>These Pain Killers are reviewed by IlmHub Team Tylenol All Tylenol except GEL CAPS click link
Tylenol Gel Caps (All) Each solid capsule-shaped tablet, coated with red gelatin on one end and yellow on the other, printed “TYLENOL/500” on each gelatin-coated end, contains: acetaminophen 500 mg. Nonmedicinal ingredients: benzyl alcohol, castor oil, cellulose, cornstarch, D&amp;amp;C yellow No. 10, edetate calcium disodium, FD&amp;amp;C Blue No. 1 and FD&amp;amp;C Blue No. 2, FD&amp;amp;C Red No.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vitamins</title>
      <link>https://askhalal.ca/products/vitamins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askhalal.ca/products/vitamins/</guid>
      <description>These Nasal Sprays are reviewed by the IlmHub Team Garden of Life Suitable for consumption, vegan-friendly. click link
AskHalal Team ~ Supervised by Sheykh Faisal Mahmoudi </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>